At this time, our correspondent Anurag Shah Allah is bringing a big and exclusive
news related to the insurance sector.
Tell me what is the news? Yes,
see, there is good news for the general insurance companies
that for two and a half years there was
no increase in their third party insurance,
so it is absolutely certain to increase from April 1st
because the suggestions that were sought
and the proposed rates were up to 23 percent from every city, so the
insurance
companies have also given suggestions there, the transporters have
also given suggestions, the insurance
contemplation has been done, the
suggestion given by the general insurance companies
said that the proposed
increase is less and it should be
increased further, 57 percent more should be increased
and there is
not so much opposition from the transporters as we have
seen recently that the way
even the transporters talk about doing it now, but this time there is
definitely a suggestion from the transporters, in that
they have given suggestions like to better the actual calculation
and not to increase the rates at home,
but
according to the information that I got from thinking, the
suggestions have come and after that what is there
Revision is certain and this revision will be for
2019 so that it should be noted that it will be at the upper level only. For the
last two and a half years, car
insurance has not increased like third party motor insurance
and the proposed
rates are here, the increase in new cars and bikes is
high, up to 17 percent and 22
percent respectively, but for commercial vehicles like
lorries and trucks, there is
not so much increase, so
this has also been balanced by the government, for
new vehicles, where long term
insurance is given, there is a
possibility of a little more increase,
but the reverse happens, the
increase in that is quite minor, so
considering this, it will affect those who buy new vehicles,
but for the insurance companies which were waiting for two and a half years, there is
very
positive news for them that after a long wait,
from April 1, their
premium for third party motor insurance increases
and let me tell you that third
party motor insurance is a very big
statement, the 25 percent contribution of general insurance custom of Rs
2 lakh crore in general insurance sectors is  If I am talking about the
premium of third party motor insurance
then this is good news for you from the insurance company
Border New India
Assurance which two should be written enter
Amritsar Amritsar we like some which one of these two do you
like because subscribe now
more wars were fought from here
that you can take good advantage friends remember
keep an eye and news also in a good way
nominations both your da